<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>


<elutaxml xmlns="http://www.eluta.ca/elutaxml" version="1.0">

<employer>
<name>Big Digital</name>

<job>
<title>Event Technician</title>
<jobref>001</jobref>
<joburl>jeremypaquette.com/eventtech.html</joburl>
<description>
Job Description
***
We are looking for a systems technician to support an existing client in a downtown office space. It’s an exciting building, with high-profile events and state of the art technology. Main duties are:
Maintaining regular hours onsite to support day-to-day events.
Getting familiar with the technology installed in the building.
Communicating with clients and event organizers to meet technology needs.
Troubleshooting technical issues, often under pressure or on short timelines.
Operating audio and video equipment during live broadcasts.
Coordinating with existing team to cover scheduling gaps and ensure all events are supported. Some evening and weekend availability will be required.

Benefits
***
$35,000 starting salary
Two weeks’ vacation annually
Supportive team of colleagues
Exciting opportunities to work creatively and learn new skills
Working for a caring and understanding company

Requirements
***
Experienced with audio and video technology for live events
Familiar with video flow/routing, common codecs, and file types
Familiar with the Microsoft suite of products and services, especially Skype and PowerPoint
Capable in Adobe Suite, including AfterEffects and Photoshop
Great communication skills. This is a client-facing position in a professional environment.
Reliable and punctual
Strong references for both personal and technical skills

Extras
***
Please detail any experience with the following:

Dante media networking
Pandoras Box media server
Production video switching and character generator (CG) systems
Digital signage technology
Computer networking and/or programming
Web and graphic design
Lighting control systems
Successful applicants will be asked to interview over the phone, followed by interviews with both the onsite team and company management.
</description>

<occupationcategory>Technology and Digital Media</occupationcategory>
<jobpostalcode>M5A 1S9</jobpostalcode>
<jobtype>fulltime</jobtype>
<salarymin>35000</salarymin>
<salarymax>35000</salarymax>
<salarytype>yearly</salarytype>
<postdate>January 31, 2018</postdate>
<expirydate>February 28, 2018</expirydate>

</job>
</employer>
</elutaxml>
